我不得不说  佩妮  这真有意思
I must say, Penny, this is great fun.
很高兴你玩得这么嗨
Glad you're enjoying yourself.
认识你和伯纳黛特前  我的洗手间之旅
Until I met you and Bernadette, my trips to the bathroom
只有排泄这一个主题
had been entirely focused on elimination.
现在又多了社交功能
Now they have a delightful social aspect.
艾米  你之前肯定跟别的女生
Amy, you must've been in the bathroom
一起上过卫生间吧
with other women before.
当然咯
Of course I have.
但之前都是陌生人  而且在我
But they were strangers and seemed off-put
跟她们隔着小间闲聊时都很不高兴
when I engaged in friendly stall-to-stall chit-chat.
有些女生不喜欢在没穿内裤时
Some women don't like to get chummy
被人套近乎
when their panties are down.
你在里面没事吧  闺蜜
You okay in there, bestie?
我没事
I'm fine...
我这么问你是因为很多人
The reason I ask is that many people
都会"膀胱羞涩"
experience bladder shyness;
就是在聊天的时候没法小...
the inability to pass uri...
喂  我说了我没事了  住嘴吧
Yeah, I said I'm fine. Stop talking to me.
她小便的时候总是这么凶吗
She always this crabby when she urinates?
其实我俩没那么铁
We're really not that close.
去他娘的  待会儿再说吧
Screw it. I'll go later.
那我待会儿还来陪你
And I'll be right by your side.
我有没有跟你说过普丽娅邀请了
Did I tell you Priya invited
我和霍华德去跟她和莱纳德一起吃饭
me and Howard to have dinner with her and Leonard?
哦  不错啊
Oh, that's nice.
非也非也
No, it's not.
她在耍花招
It's a strategic maneuver.
莱纳德的新女友在检验伯纳黛特
Leonard's new girlfriend is testing Bernadette's loyalty
对你和咱们的忠心呢
to you and the group.
那个贱人真狡猾啊
That bitch is crafty.
-真的吗  -当然
- You think? - Of course.
猎豹是怎么对付牛羚群的
How does the cheetah attack a herd of wildebeests?
追杀最弱小的成员
By going after its weakest member.
为啥我是最弱小的
Well, what makes me the weakest member?
因为你总轻信别人  而且身材瘦小
Your trusting nature coupled with your teeny-tiny body.
你要是在塞伦盖蒂连一分钟都撑不到
You wouldn't last a minute on the Serengeti.
好吧  艾米  你这是在犯傻
Okay, Amy, you're being silly.
谁跟谁一起吃饭我才不在乎呢
I'm not concerned about who hangs out with who.
而且我肯定对莱纳德那个
And I certainly don't have a problem
总是化妆太浓的新女友没啥意见
with Leonard's new girlfriend who wears way too much makeup.
呜  这鞋好漂亮
Ooh, these are cute.
当然我要是买下的话
Of course if I buy them,
我就得给同性恋夫妇当代孕妈妈了
I'll have to rent my womb out to a gay couple.
无所谓了  我跟她说我去不了
It doesn't matter. I'm going to tell her we can't make it.
不行  你一定要去
Oh, no. You have to go.
我不懂了
I don't understand.
我以为我是那只瘦小的牛羚
I thought I was a teeny-tiny wildebeest.
没错  而且你还在用草莓香味的香波
You are-- with hair that smells like strawberries.
我们要充分利用这一点
And we're going to use that to our advantage.
打住  你到底在说什么
Wait. What are you talking about?
只要接受了邀请  伯纳黛特就成了
By accepting the invitation, Bernadette becomes
敌营里的双面间谍
a double agent inside the enemy camp.
她可以洞悉普丽娅的诡计
She could ferret out Priya's tactics,
找到她的弱点
identify her weaknesses
并能提供假情报  比如
and feed her false information, such as:
莱纳德是地下斗鸡比赛的常客
Leonard's no stranger to back-alley cockfights.
不知道啊  我不怎么会撒谎的
I don't know. I'm not a very good liar.
在天主学校时就被罚得不敢撒谎了
They kind of whup that out of you in Catholic school.
别担心  我来教你
Don't worry. I'll teach you.
我在童子军里待了两年
I did two years of Cub Scouts
都没让他们发现我是女生
before they found out I was a girl.
好吧  我不认识你们
Okay, I don't know you people.
我只是个天真的女生
I'm just an innocent woman wondering
不知这家鞋店能否用德士古加油卡
if this shoe store will take my Texaco card.
你觉得在你的双峰之间藏一个
How do you feel about concealing a recording device
录音设备怎么样
in the cleavage of your ample bosom?
我双峰之间容不下任何东西
I don't want anything in my ample bosom.
来嘛  小草莓  为咱们牺牲一下呗
Come on, Strawberries. Take one for the team.
生活大爆炸
第四季第二十二集
-好  待会儿见  -好消息
- Okay, see you later. - Good news.
我终于设计出了三人象棋
I finally have a handle on my idea for three-person chess.
确实是好消息  拜拜
That is good news. Bye.
你知道我是怎么解决
Uh, do you know how I solved
交战区域中心对称这个问题的吗
the balanced center combat-area problem?
很简单
Five words:
四边形向三角形的过渡镶嵌
transitional quadrilateral to triangular tessellation.
这  这个很赞
That... that's brilliant.
我就说嘛
It's what I do.
等下  还有哈
But wait, there's more.
我还发明了两个新棋子
I also invented two new chess pieces.
毒蛇  和老妇
The serpent... and the old woman.
好吧  现在我非得问了  这俩怎么玩
Okay, now I have to ask. What do they do?
当毒蛇经过对方的棋子时
When the serpent slithers to an opposing player's piece,
那个棋子就算中毒了
that piece is considered poisoned
再走两步之后就会死掉
and will die after two more moves.
好吧
All right.
除非  它能及时赶到老妇身边
Unless... it gets to the old woman in time,
这样的话她就能吸出毒液
in which case she sucks out the poison,
并且自己变成太后
turning her into the Grand Empress:
老妇同时集合了
a piece combining the power
马  后和毒蛇三者的功效
of the Knight, Queen and Serpent.
妙极了
Elegant.
那是因为简单才妙
That's because it's simple.
好  很期待和你杀一局哦
Okay, well, I look forward to playing with you.
还有
And...
还有啥
And what?
第三个人啊
And a third person.
这是三人象棋嘛
It's three-person chess.
我不得不说  自从你开始
I must say, ever since you started
定期交媾之后  你的脑子就没那么好使了
having regular intercourse, your mind has lost its keen edge.
你应该采取点儿措施的
You should reflect on that.
抱歉  可爱因斯坦性生活也很频繁啊
Excuse me, but Einstein had a pretty busy sex life.
所以他没能把引力和其它力统一起来
Yes, and he never unified gravity with the other forces.
他要是不这么乱搞
If he hadn't been such a hound dog,
我们早就有时光机器了
we'd all have time machines.
知道了  拜
Got it. Bye.
你知道哥是对的
You know I'm right.
他的病情又加重了
I think he's getting worse.
嗷  我的跖骨在哀嚎
Oh, my metatarsal are barking.
-你还好吗  -没事
- You okay? Yeah, yeah.
我只是穿了双新鞋而已
I'm just breaking in some new shoes.
-很漂亮  -谢谢
- Very pretty. - Thank you.
你知道女人穿高跟鞋
Did you know that women wear high heels
是为了更加前凸后翘吗
to make the buttocks and breasts more prominent?
还真没这么想过
Hadn't really thought about it.
瞧
Look.
呃  没错  相当...翘
Uh, sure. Very... prominent.
拜托  莱纳德  别乱瞟了
Please, Leonard, don't leer,
你有女友了
you have a girlfriend.
抱歉
Sorry.
你要和普丽娅  霍华德
So, are you off to dinner
伯纳黛特共进晚餐吗
with Priya, Howard and Bernadette?
是啊  你怎么知道的
Yeah. How did you know?
我在商场听说的
I heard it at the mall,
当时正和闺蜜们一起血拼
when I was shopping with my girlfriends,
这基本上就是我现在的生活状态了
'cause, you know, that's kind of my life now.
祝你有愉快的一晚
Have a good night.
我转身离开时  尽量别偷瞄我的翘臀
Try not to ogle my caboose as I walk away.
拉杰  你要和我们共进晚餐吗
Hey, Raj, will you be joining us for dinner?
孤家寡人跟两对甜蜜鸳鸯掺和吗
The lonely guy and the two happy couples?
我还不如找个猥琐男
I'd rather get a prostate exam
帮我做前列腺检查直到他断指呢
from a leper who walks away with nine fingers.
你能不能不要顾影自怜了
Oh, would you please stop feeling sorry for yourself?
我也是迫于无奈
I have to feel sorry for myself.
因为我是唯一关心自己的人
I'm the only one who cares.
就像我是唯一愿意和自己做爱的人一样
Just like I'm the only one who'll have sex with me.
你怎么能在你妹妹面前说这种话
Really? In front of your sister?
我们从小住在一个房间
We shared a room growing up.
我都听习惯了
This is not news to me.
失陪了  我要去街上独自闲逛一会
Excuse me. I'm going to go wander the streets alone.
无人关注  无人需要  无人爱怜
Invisible, unwanted and unloved.
都市里的一剪孤影  无牵无挂
A pathetic shadow in a city with no heart.
我忘穿防风夹克了  外面怪冷的
I forgot my windbreaker. It'chilly.
我就不明白了  新鞋就这样穿的吗
I don't understand. Is this a way to break in new shoes?
不  但这对小宝贝一旦沾地
No. Once these puppies touch the ground
就属于我了  我就要穿着它们
they're mine, and I'll have to wear them
在好莱坞大道徘徊
walking up and down Hollywood Boulevard
好让它们物有所值
in order to pay them off.
美啦  美啦  美啦
Pretty, pretty, pretty.
好消息  牛羚到达印度人家了
Good news: the wildebeest is in the curry.
神马
The what?
伯纳黛特同普丽娅和莱纳德碰面了
Bernadette is with Priya and Leonard.
短信已收到
Message received.
启动"普丽娅不想步你后尘"行动
Commence operation "Priya Wouldn't Wanna Be-ya."
你不至于吧
Hey. Seriously?
你高中没玩够这种小团体把戏吗
Didn't you get enough of this cliquey crap in high school?
我倒也想  但组小团体是需要朋友的
I wish. A clique requires friends.
-而我却没有  -一个都没有吗
- I didn't have any. - None?
我以前会把午餐带到保全室
I used to take my lunch down to the maintenance room
和清洁工一起吃
and eat with the janitor.
那种感觉很好  直到他老婆骂我"贱货"
It was nice until his wife called me a puta
将我拒之门外
and made me stop.
等等
Hang on.
是牛羚发来的
It's the wildebeest.
普丽娅刚刚挖苦了一番你的演艺事业
Priya just made a snide comment about your acting career.
她都说什么了
W-What the hell did she say?
她认为  了不起的是你勇于追梦
She thinks it's cool you're following your dream,
不管这有多难
no matter what.
贱人!
That bitch!
你想怎么应对
How do you want to handle it?
呃  好吧
Um, okay.
让伯纳黛特告诉普丽娅
Tell Bernadette to tell Priya that
我在去布拉格的路上
I'm on my way to Prague
准备去和安吉丽娜·朱莉拍电影
to shoot a movie with Angelina Jolie.
明白
Got it.
是3D电影吗
Is it going to be in 3-D?
什么  无所谓  这个不重要
What? I don't know. It doesn't matter.
还是说3D电影吧
I'm gonna say 3-D.
可以让她知道制片方对电影很有信心
That'll let her know the studio has faith in it.
开什么玩笑  竟然是3D的
You're kidding. 3-D?
听说是这样的
That's what I hear.
那制片方一定对电影很有信心
Then the studio must have real faith in it.
她为什么没告诉我呢
Wonder why she didn't tell me.
你最近经常和你的前女友接触吗
Have you been spending time with your ex-girlfriend?
没有
No...
那她没告诉你有什么好奇怪的
Then why are you surprised she didn't tell you?
与其说是"奇怪"
Well, it's not as much "surprised" as...
不如说是  另一种感觉
you know... uh... the other thing.
什么感觉
What other thing?
如果你  呃
Well, if you... uh...
我不
I don't... oh...
我想说的是哪个词来着
What's the word I'm looking for?
我不会帮你的  看你的囧样太欢乐了
I'm not going to help you. This is hilarious.
她还在和宇航员谈恋爱
She's also dating an astronaut.
哇哦  这么厉害啊
Wow. That's very impressive.
是啊  但莱纳德也很厉害啊
Yeah. But Leonard's impressive, too.
谢谢
Thank you.
糊涂
"Befuddled."
"糊涂"这个词很合适
The word I was looking for was "befuddled."
马走到老妇...
Knight to Old Woman...
6又1/3位置
six-and-a-third.
妙棋
Brilliant move.
多谢夸奖
Thank you.
两位失陪一下
Will the two of you excuse me?
抱抱我吧
I need a hug.
抱歉  我家有客人
Sorry, I have company.
拜托  谢尔顿  开开门
Come on, Sheldon, open the door.
我不想抱你
I don't want to hug you.
我也不想抱你
I don't want to hug you, either.
我只是感觉很郁闷[蓝色]
I was just feeling blue.
蓝色  就是郁闷的意思
Blue, as in depressed.
还没郁闷到孤独的地步
Well, not so much depressed as lonely.
我不知道孤独是什么颜色
I don't know what color lonely is.
-什么  -红色代表愤怒
- What? - Red is angry;
黄色代表惊恐
yellow is frightened;
绿色代表嫉妒  蓝色代表忧郁
green is jealous; and blue is depressed.
没准咱可以找个颜色来代表孤独
Perhaps we can assign a color to lonely.
橙色跟啥都不押韵  没准橙色也觉得挺孤独的
Nothing rhymes with orange. It's probably lonely.
好吧  进来吧
All right. Come in.
你看起来的确挺橙挺孤独的
You look positively orange with loneliness.
不行  说起来还是不顺嘴
No, I don't see that catching on at all.
你在干嘛呢
What are you doing?
我在研究我的三人国际象棋
I'm working on my three-person chess game.
真酷  我能一起玩吗
Oh, cool. Can I play?
这是三人象棋
It's three-person chess.
你带朋友来了吗
Did you bring a friend?
没
No.
那我就只好请你思考一下
Then as a mental exercise I invite you
为啥咱俩人
to figure out why the two of us
没法玩三人象棋了
can't play three-person chess.
这家伙够迷糊的吧
Can you believe this guy?
然而鉴于人际交往的需要
Social protocol does, however,
我应该在你孤独的时候
require me to bring you a hot beverage
给你来杯热饮
in your time of need.
不用了  谢谢  我没事
No, thank you. I'm fine.
你没的选择
It's not optional.
我们家没茶了  但愿你喜欢牛肉汤
We're out of tea. I hope you like bouillon.
我猜你大概在琢磨
I, uh, I guess you're probably wondering
我为什么会这么郁闷
what's got me down.
实际上我在琢磨
Actually, I was wondering
我能不能再加一个新的棋子
if I could add a third new chess piece.
你觉得我加个乔伊王子怎么样
How do you think people would feel about Prince Joey--
他是国王弱智但却心地善良的表弟
the king's feeble-minded but well-meaning cousin?
我就快三十岁了
I'm going to be 30 years old,
但我却找不到一个爱我的人
and I have no one in my life to love me.
我真是没救了  我不喝酒的话
I'm such a basket case, I can't even talk to a woman
都没法开口跟女人讲话
without having alcohol in my body.
乔伊王子有趣的地方就在于
The fun thing about Prince Joey
他每动一次  就有百分之二十的几率
is every time he moves, there's a one-in-five chance
会自杀
he'll kill himself.
谢尔顿  听我说
Sheldon, listen to me.
我要做个重大的决定  而我很害怕
I have a big decision to make, and I'm scared.
很黄很害怕  说吧
Yellow. Go ahead.
我在药学院的一个朋友
A friend at the School of Pharmacology
给了我这些他们正在测试的药
gave me these new pills they're testing.
他说这将是治疗社交焦虑障碍领域的
He says it's the next big thing
又一奇迹
for social anxiety disorder.
有意思  这药是什么成分的
Fascinating. What's in it?
我也不知道
I'm not sure.
某种β受体阻断剂跟从牛的尿液中
Some sort of beta-blocker attached to a molecule
提取的分子的混合物
extracted from the urine of cows.
我喜欢牛
I like cows.
这不是重点
That's not the point.
你怎么想不重要  继续说吧
It was its own point. Go on.
我是个科学家
I'm a scientist.
我靠我的思考能力吃饭
My ability to think is my bread and butter.
我怕我吃了这个药以后  可能会丧失那些
I'm afraid if I take this, I might lose
让我在我的领域里
that special, unique something
如此成功的特质
that makes me so successful in my field.
拉杰  我有幸
Rajesh, I've had the privilege
跟你一起共事了多年
of working alongside you for many years.
我建议你就跟吃糖豆一样
My recommendation is that
把这些药都吞了吧
you gobble these up like Tic Tacs.
好吧  我还在琢磨这事呢
Okay, I'm still trying to work this out.
佩妮是怎么搭上一个宇航员的
How did Penny meet an astronaut?
我也不知道
I don't know.
就正常这么搭上的呗
The regular way people meet astronauts.
宇航员大多都住在德克萨斯州呀
Most of those guys live in Texas.
显然这哥们儿不住那儿
Obviously, this one doesn't.
好吧
Okay.
莱纳德住在美国  而普丽娅是印度来的
Leonard lives here. Priya's from India.
结果不也认识了嘛  霍华德  你搞什么
People meet, Howard. God!
好吧
Fine.
你也认识过不少宇航员
You've met lots of astronauts,
我可从来都没拷问你是怎么认识的
and I've never grilled you about that.
谢谢你以怨报德
I'd thank you to extend me the same courtesy.
我没拷问你  我只是好奇而已
I'm not grilling you; I was just curious.
我还在琢磨她居然要出演大片这件事呢
I still can't get over the fact that she got a big movie part.
倒不是因为我在乎我前女友的事  我真不在乎
Not that I care what my ex-girlfriend's up to, 'cause I don't.
也许她就是在片场认识那个宇航员的呢
Maybe that's where she met the astronaut, all right?
不好意思  可是宇航员
I'm sorry. What would an astronaut be doing
跑到片场去干嘛呀
working on a movie?
他是顾问
He's a consultant.
你不是说这部电影是关于十八世纪的维也纳的吗
I thought the movie was about 18th-century Vienna.
他就不能有点业余爱好吗
He can't have a hobby?!
失陪一下  我要去洗手间了
Excuse me, I have to pee.
你们是不是觉得这件事也很不可思议
Or is that implausible, as well?!
两对情侣一起玩就是好  对吧
It's nice to have another couple to hang with, isn't it?
好了  宝贝儿  你们得回家了
All right, guys, you have to go back.
我可负担不起你们
I can't afford you.
不  别抛弃我们  我们爱你
No, don't send us away; we love you.
我也爱你们  但你们比我的房租还贵
I love you, too, but you cost more than my rent.
但是佩妮  你穿上我们之后很漂亮呀
But, Penny, you look so good in us.
该死的  鞋说的对
Damn it, the shoes are right.
天啊  佩妮  你还是真是鬼点子多多呀
Good golly, Penny, your whimsy is boundless.
进展如何了  牛羚
What do you got for me, wildebeest?
我觉得他们在逼问我
I think they're on to me.
这故事开始漏洞百出了
The story's starting to fall apart.
冷静点  没事的
Calm down. Everything's going to be okay.
我们或许得杀她灭口了
We may have to kill her.
伯纳黛特  我开免提了
Bernadette, I'm putting you on speakerphone.
你在哪呢
Where are you now?
在洗手间
In the bathroom.
不错嘛
Oh, look at this,
又一次经典的洗手间对话
another one of our classic bathroom gabfests.
到底是怎么回事
What's the problem?
他们在问我
They're just asking me
一堆我回答不上来的问题
all sorts of questions I can't answer.
那就换话题呀
Just change the subject.
我想我应该可以让他们继续聊
I suppose I could get them back to talking about Leonard
莱纳德去印度见普丽娅父母的事
going to India to meet Priya's parents.
什么
What?!
他们好像说今年夏天一起去印度
They said something about going there this summer.
什么  他们要订婚吗
What, are they getting engaged?
我不知道  我忙着自圆其说呢
I don't know. I was too busy covering my heinie
都是艾米说什么宇航员害的
on Amy's stupid astronaut story!
什么宇航员
What astronaut story?
你短信说佩妮在跟个宇航员约会
You texted me Penny's dating an astronaut.
我发的是"建筑师"  真好玩
I texted "architect." That's amusing.
肯定是自动纠错帮我改的
Auto-correct must've changed it.
是啊  太好笑了
Yeah, it's hysterical.
好吧  反正别提宇航员的事了
All right, look, just forget about the astronaut.
是建筑师  你上哪去认识宇航员
Architect. Where would you have met an astronaut?
一定要问去印度怎么回事就好了
Look, just find out what's up with this trip to India.
我再也不想干这事了
I don't want to do this anymore!
你敢
Don't you quit on us!
妮妮  你没事吧
Bernie, you okay?
原来是个建筑师
It was an architect!
谢谢你陪我来  谢尔顿
Thank you for coming with me, Sheldon.
真够朋友
You're a good friend.
很高兴你这么想
I'm glad you think so.
我就是想让你这么认为
That's what I strive to emulate.
好吧  来看看这药有没有效
Okay, let's see if this drug works.
有事吗
Can I help you?
抱歉这么盯着你看  你太美了
Forgive me for staring, but you're very beautiful.
谢谢
Thank you.
你口音真好听  你家乡是
That's a great accent. Where are you from?
印度
India.
真好  我一直想去那儿
Oh, cool. I've always wanted to go there.
印度很漂亮  你一定会喜欢的
It's a beautiful country. You'd love it.
能坐这里吗
May I join you?
好的  当然  有何不可
Uh, okay, sure. Why not?
我是拉杰·库萨帕里博士
My name is Dr. Rajesh Koothrappali,
这位是我朋友谢尔顿·库珀博士
and this is my friend Dr. Sheldon Cooper.
不用理我
There's no need to interact with me.
我只是来观察的
I'm just here to observe.
他在观察什么
What's he observing?
我们是科学家  啥都观察的
We're scientists. We observe everything.
给  去买个松饼吃
Here, go buy yourself a scone.
好吧
All right.
-那你叫什么  -安吉拉
- And what is your name? - Angela.
这名字来源于天使  很恰当
Oh, derived from the word "angel." Appropriate.
你真可爱
You're cute.
我要买个松饼
I'd like to buy a scone.
抱歉  卖完了
Oh, I'm sorry, we're out.
还有小松饼要吗
We have muffins.
听起来很好吃
They sound delicious,
但这钱是专用来买松饼的
but this money is earmarked for scones.
你在做什么
What are you doing?!
只是觉得这样舒服
Oh, just getting comfortable.
你在洛杉矶住多久了
So how long have you lived in Los Angeles?
我...
I...
松饼卖完了
They were out of scones.
谢尔顿  我在跟人说话
Sheldon, I'm talking to someone.
你这样太没礼貌了
You're being rude.
我敢打赌你肯定是演员
I'll bet you're an actress.
不是的话太可惜了
If not, you should be.
你有这么出众的脸蛋
You have a very expressive face.
天哪
Oh, my God.
等等  你这是去哪儿
Wait, where are you going?
我们挺聊得来的啊
We were doing so well.
她还没来得及见我小弟弟呢
She never even got to see my penis.
谁还要咖啡
Who wants some more coffee?
-谢谢  我要  -我也要
- Thanks, yeah. - Sure.
我来帮你吧
Let me help you.
很高兴女孩子们相处融洽
Nice to see that the gals are getting along.
"女孩子们"
"Gals"?
你谁呀  摩登原始人吗
Who are you, Fred Flintstone?
印度之旅一定会好玩的
This trip to India sounds fun.
是啊  我也这么觉得
Yeah, I think it will be.
你担心自己父母不接受莱纳德吗
Are you concerned your parents might not approve of Leonard?
有点
A little.
他们挺守旧的
They're very old-fashioned.
换我就不会担心
Well, I wouldn't worry about it.
你们又不是去订婚  是吧
It's not like you guys are getting engaged, right?
天哪  不是  我们还没到那阶段
Oh, God, no. We're not there yet.
不是订婚  有意思
Not engaged. Very interesting.
我要去趟洗手间
I have to tinkle.
你今晚去过好多趟了  没事吧
You've been in there a lot tonight. Are you okay?
没事  你准备写进书里吗
Yes. Are you writing a book?
你为什么这么生气
Why are you getting upset?
我才没生气  你才生气
I'm not upset. Maybe you're upset.
你怎么了
What's up with you?
伯纳黛特
Bernadette?
我再也做不下去了
I can't do this anymore!
我是个好女孩
I'm a good girl!
我上的是天主教学校
I went to Catholic school!
好吧  很晚了
Okay, well, it's getting late.
今晚很愉快
This was terrific.
你赢了
You win.
妮妮
Bernie?
我想你要说的是  "糊涂了"
I think the word you're looking for is "befuddled."
我的弹弓把我的象
My catapult flings my bishop
弹到霍华德的后的G2位置上
to Howard's Queen's Gorilla two.
妙招啊
Nice.
车进入传送板
Okay, Rook to transporter pad.
然后来到了
And he comes out at...
莱纳德的后的B5又1/3位置上
...Leonard's Queen's Bishop five-and-a-third.
将莱纳德的军
Check on Leonard.
等等
Hang on.
我的兵何时允许用高尔夫车
When is my Pawn allowed to use the golf cart?
等它冲完电
When it's done charging.
或等你登陆到时光机器上
Or you land on the time machine.
很明显
Obviously.
养蜂人走到K12位置
Beekeeper to King 12.
我俘获你的教皇  释放了蜂群
I capture your Pope and release the Swarm.
将死谢尔顿
Checkmate on Sheldon.
我就知道该让教皇装上喷气背包的
I knew I should've given my Pope the jet pack.
哇  看来有两个人赢了哦
Hey, I've got winners.